{
	"cards": [
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-15-tag-multiple-choice-card-1",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"ruling out specific medical conditions based on the absence of certain signs and symptoms.",
					"the EMT’s prediction of the type of illness a patient has based on how the call is dispatched.",
					"your awareness and concern for potentially serious underlying and unseen injuries or illness.",
					"determining the underlying cause of a patient’s medical condition based on signs and symptoms."
				],
				"question": "An index of suspicion is MOST accurately defined as:",
				"source": "See Patient Assessment"
			},
			"back": "your awareness and concern for potentially serious underlying and unseen injuries or illness."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-15-tag-multiple-choice-card-2",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"is a more contagious type of disease.",
					"leads to chronic infection after exposure.",
					"has a greater ability to produce disease.",
					"is less resistant to treatment."
				],
				"question": "Hepatitis B is more virulent than hepatitis C, which means that it:",
				"source": "See Common or Serious Communicable Diseases"
			},
			"back": "has a greater ability to produce disease."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-15-tag-multiple-choice-card-3",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"joint pain, muscle aches, and blurred vision.",
					"fever, rash, nausea, and difficulty breathing.",
					"crushing chest pain, vomiting, and weakness.",
					"headache, low back pain, and arm numbness."
				],
				"question": "Typical chief complaints in patients with an infectious disease include:",
				"source": "See Infectious Diseases"
			},
			"back": "fever, rash, nausea, and difficulty breathing."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-15-tag-multiple-choice-card-4",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"reassessing the nature of illness.",
					"reviewing all treatment performed.",
					"taking another set of vital signs.",
					"repeating the primary assessment."
				],
				"question": "Reassessment of a patient with a medical complaint should begin by:",
				"source": "See Patient Assessment"
			},
			"back": "repeating the primary assessment."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-15-tag-multiple-choice-card-5",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"are bleeding.",
					"have a fever.",
					"vomit.",
					"cough."
				],
				"question": "Patients with tuberculosis pose the greatest risk for transmitting the disease when they:",
				"source": "See Common or Serious Communicable Diseases"
			},
			"back": "cough."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-15-tag-multiple-choice-card-6",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"50-year-old woman with moderate obesity",
					"12-year-old child with a fractured arm",
					"39-year-old man with mild hypertension",
					"68-year-old woman with type 2 diabetes"
				],
				"question": "Which of the following patients is at greatest risk for complications caused by the influenza virus?",
				"source": "See Common or Serious Communicable Diseases"
			},
			"back": "68-year-old woman with type 2 diabetes"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-15-tag-multiple-choice-card-7",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"cardiac",
					"endocrine",
					"neurologic",
					"respiratory"
				],
				"question": "It is especially important to assess pulse, sensation, and movement in all extremities as well as pupillary reactions in patients with a suspected ___________ problem.",
				"source": "See Patient Assessment"
			},
			"back": "neurologic"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-15-tag-multiple-choice-card-8",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Sexual practices",
					"Drug allergies",
					"HIV status",
					"Recent travel"
				],
				"question": "In addition to obtaining a SAMPLE history and asking questions related to the chief complaint, what else should you specifically inquire about when assessing a patient with a potentially infectious disease?",
				"source": "See Infectious Diseases"
			},
			"back": "Recent travel"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-15-tag-multiple-choice-card-9",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"is typically limited to a focused exam for patients who are unconscious.",
					"should be performed at the scene, especially if the patient is critically ill.",
					"is not practical if the patient is critically ill or your transport time is short.",
					"should routinely include a comprehensive examination from head to toe."
				],
				"question": "The secondary assessment of a medical patient:",
				"source": "See Patient Assessment"
			},
			"back": "is not practical if the patient is critically ill or your transport time is short."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-15-tag-multiple-choice-card-10",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"is focused on the nature of illness, the patient’s chief complaint, and his or her symptoms.",
					"is not as complex for the EMT because most patients typically present with classic symptoms.",
					"almost exclusively focuses on physical signs that indicate the patient is experiencing a problem.",
					"requires a thorough head-to-toe exam that involves a detailed assessment of all body systems."
				],
				"question": "In contrast to the assessment of a trauma patient, assessment of a medical patient:",
				"source": "See Patient Assessment"
			},
			"back": "is focused on the nature of illness, the patient’s chief complaint, and his or her symptoms."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-15-tag-multiple-choice-card-11",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"direct your partner to apply oxygen via nonrebreathing mask.",
					"squeeze the trapezius muscle to see if the patient responds.",
					"assess breathing depth and determine the respiratory rate.",
					"attempt to elicit a verbal response by talking to the patient."
				],
				"question": "Upon initial contact with a patient who appears to be unconscious, you should:",
				"source": "See Patient Assessment"
			},
			"back": "attempt to elicit a verbal response by talking to the patient."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-15-tag-multiple-choice-card-12",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"meningitis.",
					"MERS-CoV.",
					"hepatitis.",
					"tuberculosis."
				],
				"question": "A patient who presents with a headache, fever, confusion, and red blotches on his or her skin should be suspected of having:",
				"source": "See Common or Serious Communicable Diseases"
			},
			"back": "meningitis."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-15-tag-multiple-choice-card-13",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"the invasion of the human body by a bacterium that cannot be destroyed by antibiotics or other drugs.",
					"a disease that can be spread from one person or species to another through a number of mechanisms.",
					"a medical condition caused by the growth and spread of small, harmful organisms within the body.",
					"any disease that enters the body via the bloodstream and renders the immune system nonfunctional."
				],
				"question": "An infectious disease is MOST accurately defined as:",
				"source": "See Infectious Diseases"
			},
			"back": "a medical condition caused by the growth and spread of small, harmful organisms within the body."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-15-tag-multiple-choice-card-14",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"quickly access the patient.",
					"notify law enforcement.",
					"contact medical control.",
					"take standard precautions."
				],
				"question": "After sizing up the scene of a patient with a possible infectious disease, your next priority should be to:",
				"source": "See Infectious Diseases"
			},
			"back": "take standard precautions."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-15-tag-multiple-choice-card-15",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"failure to be vaccinated against any strain of hepatitis.",
					"prolonged hospitalization, especially in an intensive care unit.",
					"a history of a respiratory illness within the past 6 to 8 weeks.",
					"prior exposure to Mycobacterium tuberculosis."
				],
				"question": "Factors that increase the risk for developing methicillin-resistant Staphylococcus aureus (MRSA) include:",
				"source": "See Common or Serious Communicable Diseases"
			},
			"back": "prolonged hospitalization, especially in an intensive care unit."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-15-tag-multiple-choice-card-16",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Asking questions related to the chief complaint",
					"Refraining from asking open-ended questions",
					"Trending of the patient’s vital signs over time",
					"Focusing solely on how the call is dispatched"
				],
				"question": "Which of the following will MOST reliably allow you to determine the nature of a patient’s illness?",
				"source": "See Patient Assessment"
			},
			"back": "Asking questions related to the chief complaint"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-15-tag-multiple-choice-card-17",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"typically does not require the EMT to contact medical control.",
					"focuses on definitive care because a diagnosis can usually be made.",
					"addresses the patient’s symptoms more than the actual disease process.",
					"involves transport only until treatment can be performed at the hospital."
				],
				"question": "The primary prehospital treatment for most medical emergencies:",
				"source": "See Management, Transport, and Destination"
			},
			"back": "addresses the patient’s symptoms more than the actual disease process."
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-15-tag-multiple-choice-card-18",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Primary assessment",
					"Baseline vital signs",
					"Index of suspicion",
					"Medical history"
				],
				"question": "When assessing a patient with a medical complaint, which of the following would MOST likely reveal the cause of the problem?",
				"source": "See Patient Assessment"
			},
			"back": "Medical history"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-15-tag-multiple-choice-card-19",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"Ibuprofen",
					"Aspirin",
					"Albuterol",
					"Oral glucose"
				],
				"question": "Which of the following medications would the EMT be LEAST likely to administer to a patient with a medical complaint?",
				"source": "See Management, Transport, and Destination"
			},
			"back": "Ibuprofen"
		},
		{
			"id": "category-chapter-15-tag-multiple-choice-card-20",
			"front": {
				"choices": [
					"wear a HEPA mask when treating any respiratory patient.",
					"routinely place a surgical mask on all respiratory patients.",
					"ask all patients if they have recently traveled abroad.",
					"get vaccinated against diphtheria, tetanus, and pertussis."
				],
				"question": "The BEST way to prevent infection from whooping cough is to:",
				"source": "See Common or Serious Communicable Diseases"
			},
			"back": "get vaccinated against diphtheria, tetanus, and pertussis."
		}
	],
	"category": {
		"value": "chapter-15",
		"label": "Chapter 15"
	},
	"tags": [
		{
			"value": "multiple-choice",
			"label": "Multiple Choice"
		}
	]
}